我叫巴里·艾伦
My name is Barry Allen,
是现今世上速度最快的人
and I am the fastest man alive.
在外人看来
To the outside world,
我只是个普通的鉴证专员
I'm an ordinary forensic scientist.
但在尖端科研实验室的朋友们的帮助下
But secretly, with the help of my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
我秘密地打击犯罪  寻找跟我一样的超能力者
I fight crime and find other meta-humans like me.
但是我在时间中迷失了
But I became lost in time.
我的朋友们用尽了一切办法才把我救回来
It took everything in my friends' power to bring me back,
但我们的世界也因此出现了新的威胁
and in doing so our world was opened up to new threats.
我是唯一来得及阻止他们的人
And I'm the only one fast enough to stop them.
我是闪电侠
I am the Flash.
《闪电侠》前情回顾
Previously on "The Flash"...
他只想要公交车上的超能力者
He only wants the bus metas.
他想要他们的超能力  所有人的
He wants their powers. All of them.
迪沃已经吸收了基尔戈
DeVoe has absorbed the powers of Killgore,
受害者
凶险星  布莱克·柏森  头脑风暴  矮星的能力
Hazard, Black Bison, Brainstorm, and Dwarfstar.
我要打倒迪沃
I'm gonna take DeVoe down.
正如伊兹所希望的那样
Just like Izzy would have wanted.
迪沃精心安排一切
DeVoe orchestrated everything
为了得到巴士上的人
to get the people he wanted on the bus.
这是个计划家  和斯旺一样
We got a planner, just like Thawne.
这是智力增强器
This is an intelligence booster.
最终会让他比思考者更睿智
I'll finally be able to outthink the Thinker.
-老爸  -很高兴见到你  先生
- Daddy! - Pleased to meet you, sir.
最后两位公车超能力者
The last two remaining bus metas--
珍妮特·佩蒂和艾德文·高斯
Janet Petty and Edwin Gauss.
-拉尔夫  -准备好了
- Ralph. - Ready.
展现双倍红色极弯
Enact double scarlet's speeds-turn.
-321 -等等
- Three, two, one-- - Wait!
我有了更好的主意
I got a better idea.
在这里  章鱼博士
Over here, Doc Ock.
看好了  斯普林特老师
Watch this, Master Splinter.
忍者神龟之力
Turtle power!
关掉吧
Shut it down.
好吧  再来一次
All right, let's run it again.
得让这事成功
We got to make this work.
他知道吗
Does he know that?
拉尔夫
Ralph?
Ralph!
什么
What?
请再来一次  听巴里的计划
One more time, please. Follow Barry's plan?
我可是花了宝贵的时间
You know, the one where I spent hours of my precious time
为你们编写出了现实的全息图
programming realistic holograms for you.
对了  那真是好极了
Which... bravo on that by the way.
谢谢
Thank you.
你变成巴里
Look. Just morph yourself into Barry.
到时候会有两个闪电侠  思考者会分不清
There'll be two Flashes, Thinker won't know which one is which,
我们就能迷惑他
and we'll confuse him.
应该是她吧
Kind of a "Her" actually.
拉尔夫  你没理解演习的要点
Ralph, you're missing the point of this exercise.
我理解  我只是在加一点即兴表演
No, I get it. I was just doing a little improv.
但这不是说相声
But this isn't standup comedy.
我知道  但如果你把它演完
Yeah, I know that, but if you just let it play out,
会有效果的
it would have worked.
你自己也可以即兴表演一点
You could have done some improving of your own.
3个人才是一台喜剧
Comedy comes in threes, man.
我们在努力保护你  迪沃要来了
We're trying to protect you. DeVoe's coming.
我们得准备好  所有人  好吗
We need to be ready. All of us, okay?
我还是觉得那是个不错的计划
I still think it's a pretty good plan.
我隐藏了自己的脸  救了自己
I hide my face. I save my ass.
闪 电 侠
第四季
第十七集
我们要发财了
We'd make a fortune.
一个由超级英雄组成的即兴表演小组
An improv group made up of superheroes?
我们可以把它搬去华盛顿
We can take it to Washington.
-我们就成DC漫画了  -不  拉尔夫
- We'd be the DC Comics. - No, Ralph.
即兴表演的第一准则就是回答  好
First rule of improv is say yes.
你认真训练会死吗
Would it kill you to take training seriously?
你打开脑洞会死吗
Would it kill you to open up your mind grapes just a little?
我们会成功的
Hey. We'll get there.
最终会  我们会成功的
Eventually, but we'll get there.
他把整件事当作一个笑话
He's just making a big joke out of the whole thing.
他就是这样  巴里
It's just the way he is, Barry.
我知道  但他得像英雄一样思考
I know, but I mean, he needs to think like a hero,
跟上重点
stay on point.
迪沃能考虑到一切
DeVoe's thought of everything.
我们不能匆匆应付
We can't just wing this one.
我们会解决的
Look, we'll figure it out.
我们总是可以的  对吗
We always do, right?
融点在我们的队伍了
Melting Point's on our team now.
我们再找到另外两个公交超能力者
We just have to find the other two bus metas,
就没问题了
and we'll be in good shape.
是啊
Yeah.
艾德文·高斯和珍妮特·佩蒂  我们追踪得如何了
Where are we with tracking down Edwin Gauss and Janet Petty?
-不  他...-什么
- No, no, he's-- - What?
-他还在...-我可以
- He's still...shh... - I ca--
努力解决
Working on it.
这么吵我没法工作
I can't work with all this noise.
太恶心了  哈里
That is disgusting, Harry.
真的  成熟些
Really, grow up.
你说真的吗
Really?
不是我说的
It wasn't me.
那很贵的
That was expensive.
哈里  你每次试着
Harry, look. Every time you try
定位这些人  都是一样的结果
to locate these guys, it's the same thing.
我告诉你  你把那玩意儿砸开
I'm telling you. You just crack that thing open.
-可能都坏了  -没有坏
- It's probably broken. - It's not broken!
只是找到这两个人太复杂了
It's just finding these two is complicated.
为什么
Why is that?
因为这家伙  艾德文·高斯
Because this dude, Edwin Gauss,
在艾伦从神速力出来的当天就迅速失踪了
flat out disappeared the day Allen came out of the Speed Force.
没有信用卡付款记录
No credit card charges.
没有银行取过钱  没有发过社交网络动态  什么都没有
No bank withdraws. No social media posts, nothing. Gone.
珍妮特·佩蒂呢
What about Janet Petty?
一样棘手  我问了乔
Just as tricky. I asked Joe
从警局调出她的档案
to pull her file from CCPD.
直到13岁才有了第一条记录
Her first known record wasn't until she was 13.
中城警局档案
有点像孤儿
Some sort of a nomad.
最后知道的住所  铁山监狱
Last known address: Iron Heights.
为什么入狱
What she in for?
强行入侵  非法入侵  抢劫
Trifecta of breaking and entering, trespassing, and burglary.
但我们该担心的是
But what we should be worried about is
她现在在哪  超能力是什么
where is she now and what are her powers?
那真是她的代号吗
Is that really her handle?
-纳尔  -迪沃需要这两个人
- "Null"? - Okay, well DeVoe needs both
去执行计划
of these people for whatever he has planned,
所以我们得弄清他们在哪
so we have to figure out where they are.
我可以的  艾伦  如果我可以平静点
I will, Allen, if I can get a little peace,
安静点  并且没有打扰
a little quiet, and no interruptions.
很好
Great.
-西斯斯 -穿越者
- Cisky. - Breacher?
我需要你的帮助
I need your help.
这信息有点混乱
Little bit of a mixed message here.
我在猎捕钉十字君主
I was hunting Lord Crucifer,
第十圈的领导者
leader of the Tenth Circle.
他的吸血鬼教徒伏击了我
His cult of bloodsuckers ambushed me.
-把我包围了  -所以你被攻击...
- They had me surrounded. - So you were attacked by...
被吸血鬼攻击
vampires?
数百个吸血鬼
Hundreds of vampires!
战斗很惨烈  但我设法瓦解了
The battle was fierce, but I managed to dismantle
他的整个力量
his entire force.
但当我要去了结钉十字的时候
But when I went to finish off Crucifer,
我不对劲了
something happened to me.
我的超能力消失了
My powers--they were gone.
什么意思
What do you mean?
我没法发出震波了
I couldn't vibe blast.
钉十字逃跑了
Crucifer got away.
他肯定对我的超能力做了什么手脚
He must have done something to my powers.
以前发生过这种事吗
Has this ever happened before?
从来没有
Never.
但是辛西娅总说你是个聪明人
But Cynthia always said you were an intelligent man,
熟知超能力科学
well-versed in the meta science.
很高兴听到吉普赛还记得我
I'm glad to hear Gypsy still remembers who I am.
你是她上司
Hey, you're her boss.
你肯定知道答案
You would know the answer to this.
她到底有没有休息日
Does she ever get a day off?
辛西娅对她的工作非常投入
Cynthia is very devoted to her job.
但是至于你的能力
But in regards to your skills--
好好  我来猜猜
Yeah, yeah. Let me guess.
-你认为她错了  -不是
- You think she's wrong. - No.
我想说的是我认为你能治好我
What I want to say is I think you can fix me.
那好吧  先生
Well, sir,
我们会很高兴
we would be happy to...
在极速实验室做几项测试
run some tests in the Speed Lab.
看看你的身体是否正常
You know, see if everything's okay.
谢谢你  西斯科
Thank you, Cisco.
现在我必须去喝杯茶
Now I must get some tea.
-他一次都没骂我  -没错
- He didn't insult me once. - Nope.
我只是希望我们能帮他
I just hope we can help him.
休息得如何  亲爱的
How was your rest, my love?
非常好
Wonderful.
我觉得自己更年轻
I've never felt more rejuvenated
并且准备好去实现我们的梦想了
and ready to realize our dream.
克利福德
Clifford.
我们用来实验的超能力者身上的额外暗物质
The additional dark matter from our subject metas is...
超越了宿主所能承受的范围
overwhelming this host's body.
还能撑多久
How long do we have?
照目前的速度来看
At the present rate,
还有一周左右的时间
just over a week's time.
不行
No.
我绝对不允许
I will not allow it.
也许可以调正生物量指标
It may be possible to adjust the biomass index,
重新调整能量分配
recalibrate the energy distribution--
增加你现任宿主的寿命
extend your current host's life.
奇怪了
Odd.
对于部分设计的调整
There are already plans
我们已经有了计划
for such an adjustment partially designed.
我试过同样的做法
I attempted the same course of action.
但是我在工程学方面
Though my mind for engineering
远远不如你有天赋
is nowhere near as gifted as yours.
你的头开得不错
Well, you got a good start.
几个小时之内  我就能完成这些设计了
I will be able to complete these designs within a few hours.
去休息会  亲爱的
Rest, my love.
我来处理所有的事
I will handle everything.
一向都是你在处理
You always do.
然后我们会继续搜索
And then we will continue on our search
公车上剩余的两个超能力者
for the remaining two bus metas.
你是说三个吧
You mean three.
哭泣者未被抓获
The Weeper is still at large.
是的
Yes.
三个
Three.
也许我的大脑也受到了影响
Perhaps my mind is being affected as well.
快点  使劲推
Come on, put your back into it!
再使劲点推
Put your fat back into it!
这东西真臭
This stinks, man.
这东西太重了  而你太弱了
This is too heavy, and you're too weak.
我们去拿推车吧
Let's get the big dolly.
哥们  板条箱不见了
Dude, the crate's gone.
我们得打电话给老板
We got to call the boss.
王冠正合适我
The crown fits.
我们正在搬  我正和他说
We were moving-- I was telling the guy,
这东西要搬一晚上
"It's gonna take all night to move this stuff."
记住  我们要谨慎行事
Okay, remember, let's just be discreet.
我们俩都不该来这里
Neither one of us are supposed to be here.
-你能做到吗  -猪能飞吗
- Can you do that? - Can pigs fly?
-不行  -把它们放在飞机上就能飞了
- No. - They can if you put them on an airplane.
想一下  艾伦  想想
Think, Allen, think.
好
Okay.
你的印度茶拿铁送到了
Just here with your chai latte,
韦斯特警探
Detective West.
-真是低调  -然后就不见了
- Subtle. - It was gone--
抱歉失陪一会
Will you excuse me just a sec, okay?
-发生了什么  -抢劫案
- What happened? - Robbery.
偷走了康达克王朝家族王冠
Stole the Kahndaq Dynasty family crown.
王冠是送来做博物馆展览的
It was brought here for the museum exhibition.
保安说王冠放在钢板箱里
The security guard said that it was being transported
运来这里
in a steel-plated crate,
重约九十公斤
weighs about 200 pounds.
突然间消失得无影无踪
Suddenly disappeared without a trace,
然后再出现时已经碎成渣了
and then reappeared completely smashed.
博物馆里还丢失了什么
So was anything else missing in the museum?
除了王冠  其他东西都在
Just the crown, nothing else is missing.
我应该在警戒线四周看看  检查一下吗
Should I, uh, stretch around the perimeter? Check things out?
不用
No, no.
从这里我可以看出  要造成这样的撞击
I mean, I can tell from here, to cause that type of impact,
箱子最起码要达到每小时88公里的速度
the case had to be moving at at least 55 miles per hour.
所以我们要找的是个超强力量超能力者
So we're looking for a meta with super strength.
可能吧
I mean, maybe.
箱子上的那些是指纹吗
Are there fingerprints on the case?
我会采集下来  再把结果发给你
I'll have them dust it, send the results in.
何必等呢  我可以直接把指纹弄下来
Why wait? I can just grab the tape.
-立刻采集到指纹  -不行
- Get the prints right now. - No, hey.
肯定是冰霜杀手
It was definitely Killer Frost,
-她看了我一眼  -拉尔夫
- and she looked at me. - Ralph!
老兄
Dude!
我需要这份工作
I need this job!
艾伦  看看你干的好事
Allen! Look what you did.
你把它扔给我  是你的错  哥们
Threw it at me! That's you, bro.
去死吧  塑胶机器人  去死
Die, Plastoid, die!
再来一次
Again.
好了
All right.
我认为够了
I-- I think-- I think that's enough.
好了  你看  穿越者
All right, hey, look, Breacher,
我知道你显然非常地
I know you're clearly very...
灰心丧气
frustrated.
别紧张好吗  我们会查清楚的
Don't stress, okay? We're gonna figure this out.
只要查清楚  我们就能治好你的
And once we do, we're gonna fix it.
我保证
I promise.
西斯斯
Cisky.
听着
Look.
对不起我以前对你的态度很差
I'm sorry for the way I treated you.
但是等你治好了我
But when you fix me,
我会让辛西娅多点时间陪你的
I'll give Cynthia more time to be with you.
真的吗
Really?
真的
Yeah.
我现在饿了
Now... I'm hungry.
这个我们也可以解决
We can fix that, too.
楼下休息室里有甜甜圈
Um, there's donuts in the downstairs break room.
自己去拿吧  多种口味可选
Help yourself. It's a huge selection.
试试菠萝馅饼味的
Yeah. Try the pineapple fritters.
别忘了试试玉米片甜甜圈
And don't forget to try the nacho donuts.
真的很好吃
Those are really good.
西斯科似乎好运来了
Looks like things are looking up for your boy Cisco.
-是吗  -什么
- Yeah... - What?
是什么  他有什么毛病
What-- what is it? What is wrong with him?
真的没毛病  他的身体很健康
Nothing, really. He seems to be in good health.
他的血液没有任何异常现象
There's nothing abnormal in his bloodwork,
身体扫瞄显示他身体没有任何细胞损伤
and his body scan showed no signs of cellular damage
即使用了这么多年的震动性超能力
despite years of using vibrational powers.
那你为什么这副表情
Okay, so then why the face?
因为钉十字没有夺走他的超能力
Because Crucifer didn't take his powers from him.
而是时间
Father Time did.
他不能发震波  是因为他老了吗
He can't blast because he's getting older?
你们这样的超能力需要很多能量
Powers like yours requires a lot of energy.
当那种能量开始减少时...
And when that energy starts to dwindle--
发出震波是第一个消失的
Vibe blasts are... the first things to go.
我觉得你该告诉他
I think you have to tell him.
那他就绝对不会让我和吉普赛见面了
He's never, ever gonna let me see Gypsy if I tell him.
他估计会拿一把刀
He's probably gonna send a knife
直接穿过我的脑壳
flying right through my skull if I tell him.
他真可能会
He might.
但这是应该做的
But it's the right thing to do.
这是什么
What the...
开始化学成分分析
Initiate chemical analysis.
一个四万美元的花瓶
A $40,000 vase?
这又不是金子做的
It's not like it was made of gold.
其实是的  而且你俩
Actually it was, and you two
不能再去犯罪现场了  私人侦探也不行
can't go to crime scenes anymore, PIs or not.
别冲我摆脸色
Don't give me that look.
我只是想要加快进程
I was just trying to speed up the process
找到这个超能力者  艾伦
finding this meta, Allen.
-已经拖太久了  -等下  我们有线索了
- Which is taking forever. - Wait, we got a hit.
珍妮·威廉斯
Jeannie Williams.
等下  我们找到了多个人
Oh, wait. We got multiple hits.
简·丽思卡  朱迪·牛顿
Jane Liska, Judy Newton.
她用了大概有17个不同身份
She's used like 17 different aliases.
好吧  那我们要怎么找出她来
Okay, so how do we find her?
我们不能就这样等着她再去抢劫吧
We can't just wait for her to rob somebody else.
我们不需要
Well, we don't have to.
我们有很多她不同的外观变化
We have the many variations of her facade.
对  我们只要把这些变化加入
Right, we simply plug these many variations
面部识别系统
into the facial recognition software.
-看看能不能找到  -没错
- See if we get a hit. - Exactly right.
那玩意开始起帮助了  哈里
That's starting to come in handy, Harry.
那是四十分钟前
That's 40 minutes ago.
珍妮特·佩蒂
奥查德布鲁姆街拐角
Corner of Orchard and Broome.
奥查德布鲁姆街  那边有什么
Orchard and Broome? What's over there?
不是什么  是谁
Not what. Who.
来吧
Come on.
-你是要...  -来吧
- What do you- - Come on.
这里闻起来一股肝泥香肠味
It smells like liverwurst.
等着进去之后吧
Yeah, wait till we get inside.
开门  好了  跟着计划走
Open up! Okay, stick to the plan.
我们质问她  找出纳尔  拷上她
We question her. We find Null. We cuff her.
-知道了  -来点黑脸白脸的戏码
- Got it. - A little good cop, bad cop action.
你们是谁
Who the hell are you?
你最糟糕的噩梦
Your worst nightmare.
乔
Uh, Joe
乔·韦斯特警探  中城警局
Detective Joe West, CCPD.
我们有几个问题要问你  渣滓
We got a couple questions for you, scum bag.
只有我最亲近的朋友才能这么叫我
Hey, only my closest friends can call me that.
据说  城里来了个新扒手
Word is, there's a new cutpurse in town
爱好昂贵的珠宝
who likes fancy jewels.
最后一次简单是在这附近
Last seen in this part of town.
私人侦探  巴里·艾伦
PI Barry Allen.
-私人侦探巴里...  -给他看  给他看
- PI Barry Al- - Show him. Show him!
巴里·艾伦  我对你可了解了
Oh, Barry Allen, I know all about you.
壮丽的堕落
Spectacular fall from grace.
-真是个悲剧  -是的  谢谢
- Tragic, really. - Yes, thank you.
看一眼
Just take a look.
我们猜测她来过这里
We're guessing she came here
想要清洗珠宝
for help to wash the sparklies.
那我可真是幸运了
Oh, I should be so lucky.
我肯定不介意这么一个
Certainly wouldn't mind a drop-in
看起来可爱的姑娘来找我  懂我的意思吗
from a lovely looking lassie like this, you know what I mean?
但不幸的是  这位不是我顾客
But unfortunately not in my cards.
抱歉了  我能留着这个吗
I'm sorry. Can I keep this?
对我撒谎我可要搞死呢
I will mess you up for lying in my face.
-拉尔夫  -拉尔夫
- Ralph. - Ralph?
拉尔夫不在这  乔
There's no Ralph here. Joe--
我是乔·韦斯特警探
I'm Detective Joe West,
我是最坏的  坏警察
the baddest...dad cop
你见都没见过
you've ever come across.
我向上帝保证
As God is my witness
我没撒谎  我没有
I am not lying. I'm not.
坏了
Oopsy-daisy.
我就知道
I knew it.
乔·韦斯特不会犯错
Joe West doesn't make any mistakes.
好吧
Okay.
她去哪里了  厄尔
Where'd she go, Earl?
交易取消
Deal's off.
该死
Damn it.
手铐
Cuffs.
手铐  艾伦
Cuffs! Allen--
宝贝  你还好吗
Babe, you okay?
我只想尽快从这上边下来
I just want to get down from here as soon as possible.
也许你该试试打嗝降下来
Maybe you should try to burp yourself down
-就像查理·巴克特那样  -拉尔夫
- like Charlie Bucket. - Ralph.
《查理和巧克力工厂》中的主角小男孩
有办法了吗
Anything?
从我能看到的来说
Well, as best I can tell,
纳尔的能力了他细胞的密度
Null's powers effect the density of his cells.
你就像是被充满了氢气一样
It's like you've been filled with helium.
真棒
Terrific.
我一直认为你挺浅薄的
Always knew you were a lightweight.
-我发誓拉尔夫  -有没有办法恢复重力
- I swear Ralph- - Hey, is there a way to reengage gravitational
万有引力
Gravitational force.
结果是
Huh, turns out...
-不需要  -别放手
- not necessary. - Do not let go.
根据巴里基本的重量
Based on Barry's standard mass
还有引力G
and the gravitational force G
然后加上纳尔
and taking into account the half-life decrement
黑物质融合的半衰期
of Null's dark matter infusion,
这个效果最终会
this effect should eventually just...
逐渐消逝
wear off.
Wear off?
你的细胞恢复正常的时间
Your cells should return to normal
-大概就是...  -干什么
- right about... - What the hell?
-现在  -落地给两分
- Now. - Two for the landing,
但是撞到鼻子的声音给十分
but perfect ten for the thud noise.
你怎么还在开玩笑
Why are you joking right now?
我是说  刚才那是怎么回事
I mean ser--what the hell was that back there?
装作乔
Pretending to be Joe?
我是坚持表演  我不能暴露身份
I committed to the bit. I couldn't blow my cover.
拉尔夫  如果这是在室外发生的呢
Ralph, what if that had happened outside on the street?
我可能飞到大气层上
I could have floated away into the stratosphere
或是掉下来摔死
or fallen to my death.
我会想办法救你的
I would have figured something out.
我们找到的十二个巴士超能力者里
Out of the 12 bus metas we have found,
迪沃控制了其中七个
DeVoe is in control of seven of them.
如果他控制了纳尔  就是八个了
If he gets Null, it'll be eight.
如果他得到了她的能力
If he gets control of her powers,
我们谈论的可是你的生命
we're talking about your life here.
抱歉  我刚才在思考《迷失》的结局
Sorry, I was just thinking about the end of "Lost."
我是说  他们真的是在炼狱里吗
I mean, were they in purgatory?
凯特看上杰克什么了
What did Kate really see in Jack?
拉尔夫
Ralph.
抱歉  伙计  不过我要让你坐冷板凳了
I'm sorry, man, but I'm benching you.
-为什么  -因为你经常
- Why? - Because you're constantly
打扰我的喜剧表演
in the middle of a comedy routine
而不是做你该做的事
instead of doing what you should.
如果你把铐子给我
if you had just tossed me the cuffs,
我们现在就抓到纳尔了
we would have Null right now.
是啊  或者她可以跑出门
Yeah, or she could have ran out the door,
我伸长手趁她不注意铐上她
and I stretch the cuffs on her when she didn't see it coming.
有什么的
It's fine.
我这是为了你好
Look, I'm doing what's best for you.
不  你不是
No, you're not.
你这是为了自己
You're doing what's best for you.
显示  德沃  马尔利泽的完整生理结果
Display, complete physiological results for DeVoe, Marlize.
皮质醇水平低
Cortisol levels low.
近期出现心动过速
Recent display of tachycardia,
反覆瞳孔扩张
repetitive pupil dilation.
显示血清素水平
Display serotonin level.
319微毫克
319 nanograms.
出现于使用精神类
Levels found in patients
麻醉药物的患者中  怎么会这样
using psychoactive narcotics. How is that?
四号目标仍然在逃
Subject four's still at large.
哭泣者
制造大范围的欣快症
Created to provide widespread euphoria...
或者爱情感
Or feelings of love.
让他食用全碱性食谱怎样
What if we put him on an all-alkaline diet?
富含抗氧化剂
Full of antioxidants.
不行
Nope.
好吧  要是我们...
Okay, what if we...
要是我们制造一种超级混合剂
Oh, what if we make a super shake
富含各种酶和益生菌  怎样
full of, like, enzymes and--and--and probiotics?
这些效果都不会持续很久  西斯科
Neither of those are gonna work long-term, Cisco.
我们总得想个办法出来吧
Okay, well, we got to come up with something, right?
这家伙到底多大年纪了
I mean, how old is this guy anyway?
这家伙年纪可大了
This guy's old.
我们必须得解决这事
We have to solve this.
因为我不清楚你  但我还挺惜命的
'Cause I don't know about you, but I actually like my life.
我知道这个办法不容易做到
I know this isn't the easy answer,
但是你得告诉他
but I think you have to tell him.
西斯斯
Cisky!
是你  我们正聊起你呢
Oh, hey, you. We were just talking about you.
我尝了你所有的甜甜圈
I've tasted all your donuts.
我的解药呢
Where's my cure?
这事有点
Well, it's a little, um,
有点复杂
it's a little complicated.
但是  你很幸运  我的朋友
But! You are lucky, my friend,
因为治好你
because your fix
只需要吃一片这种
is as simple as taking one of these
粉色小药片
little pink pills.
-蓝色  -蓝色药片
- Blue. - Blue pills.
就在这
Right there.
抗主安剂
"Anta-hista-mine."
抗过敏药物
对  一片抗组胺剂
That's right, an antihistamine.
看  筋力  意思是体力
See, "Stamine," That's Latin for stamina.
你体力很旺盛
Which you have plenty of, you know.
你体力太旺盛了以至于伤害你的身体
You have so much of it that it's actually hurting you.
但这种反物质药片
But this antimatter pill--
能平衡你的体力
it's gonna level you right out.
你现在就吃了
Oh, you're taking it now.
他现在就吃了
He's--he's taking it now.
为什么我的震波放出来不一样了
Why is my vibe blast different?
我想是药物的副作用
I think it's a side effect of the pills.
还没完全调查清楚
Hasn't been thoroughly researched yet,
会有头疼  恶心
but you know, there's headaches, nausea...
不同的  震波颜色
different, uh, color vibes.
我被治好了  谢谢
I'm cured. Thank you.
小意思
Anytime.
你知道你只是让事情更糟了吗
You do realize you're just making this worse?
目前没有纳尔的信息
Nothing on Null so far.
哈里准备试试别的办法
Harry's gonna try something else.
-我们会找到她的  -我们必须找到
- We'll find her. - We have to.
即使拉尔夫竭尽全力想搞砸
Even if Ralph does everything in his power to screw it up.
巴里
Barry.
拉尔夫不是这么想的
That is not his intention.
那他可能骗了我
Well, he could have fooled me.
那是他的命  要是还有
It's his life. I mean, if there's
什么他在乎的事情  那就是丢了命
anything he cares about, it's losing it.
他要是不像我教他的那样  像我一样思考
Well, he's gonna lose it if he doesn't start
那他会没命的
thinking like me, like I taught him.
像你一样思考
Thinking like you?
他永远也做不到那样  巴里
He's never gonna do that, Barry,
你也不能指望他做到
and you can't expect him to.
中城珠宝发生了劫案
Robbery at Central City Jewelry.
兄弟  她真是喜欢珠宝
Man, she loves bling.
-我马上去  -等等  你需要后援
- I'm on it. - Wait, you need backup.
拉尔夫现在就是拖后腿的
Well, Ralph's too much of a liability right now.
他候补
He stays benched.
-凯特琳  西斯科呢  -他们和穿越者在一起
- Caitlin, Cisco? - They're with Breacher.
来不及等他俩了
It would take too long to wait for them.
-计划是什么  -计划...
- Then what's the plan? - The plan...
是"障眼法"
is "Occulation."
你说她的指尖
You said her fingertips,
会在使用能力时发光
they illuminated when she used her powers.
那意味着暗物质催化  也就是说
That means dark matter accelerant, that means
她力量来源于视神经...
powers are generating from the optic nerve--
我想说的是  纳尔无法操纵
What I'm trying to say is Null can't gravitate
看不到的东西  所以只要你在
what she cannot see, so you vibrate beyond
接近她视线的时候振动速率超过她视觉
the speed of sight as you approach her eye line--
她就看不见我
I'll be invisible to her.
-对迪沃起作用过  -试试看
- It worked against DeVoe. - Let's try it.
什么
What the...
同时有没看到的意思
意料之外啊
Didn't see that coming.
这就是目的
It's kind of the point.
不  你没料到那个
No, you didn't see that coming.
我管它叫我的跑路车
See, I call it my getaway car.
因为要么让那个人死
'Cause either the person in there dies,
要么你让我跑掉
or you let me get away.
你没事吧
You okay?
没事  呆在这儿
It's okay. Just stay here.
这个废物垃圾真是
This useless piece of trash is...
废物
useless.
我居然傻到都没法给这个废物垃圾
It's like I'm so dumb I can't even come up
找个合适的同义词
with a good synonym for this useless piece of trash.
哈里  没人可以料到
Harry, no one could have predicted
纳尔能脱掉手铐
that Null would have picked herself
或者劫持人质
out of the cuffs or taken a hostage.
你们既没法利用
Nor did either of you predict
物质的不均匀分布
the location of a 120-pound woman
造成的时空曲率
using the curvature of spacetime
判断出一个120磅重的女人的位置
caused by the uneven distribution of mass
也没计算到
yet still somehow failed to account
她头上浮着的4000磅的汽车
for the gravitational pull of a 4,000-pound car
重力牵引力
floating right above her head.
科学家们花了几十年
Scientists have spent decades
试图理解相对论和量子力学
trying to understand relativity and quantum gravity.
关键不是要理解力学  艾伦
This is not about understanding gravity, Allen.
关键是要么理解她
It's about understanding her
要么不理解她
or not understanding her.
结果是  迪沃
As it turns out, DeVoe
可以计算出人类行为
can somehow calculate human behavior.
哈里  停
Harry, stop.
我才是放走她的人
Look, I'm the one that let her get away.
-你已经尽力了  -我尽力了吗  艾伦
- You did your best. - Did I, Allen?
真的  这是第二个挣脱
Really? This is the second meta
抑制手铐的超能力者了
to evade the dampening cuffs.
已经一年了  我们有什么进展吗
It's been almost a year, and where are we?
迪沃的进展呢
And where's DeVoe?!
怎么
What?
没啥  就只是
Nothing, it's just...
你带着计划步入战场
you went out into the field, you had a plan,
计划失败了而已
and...it didn't work.
但是迪沃的计划成功了  哈里没说错
But they do for DeVoe. Harry's not wrong.
迪沃制定计划前穷尽了
DeVoe's gone over every possible outcome
所有可能
before making his plans.
我们做不到这个  哈里也做不到
Which we can't do, and neither can Harry.
那我们要做什么
Well, then what are we supposed to do?
你想我们像拉尔夫希望的那样说单口相声
I mean, you just want us to adlib like Ralph wants us to?
巴里  你没见过  但你不在的时候
Barry, you didn't see it, but when you were gone,
拉尔夫随机应变  他开玩笑
Ralph rose to the occasion. He cracked jokes.
他的思维跳出窠臼
He thought outside the box.
他按照他自己明白的方式搞定工作
I mean, he got the job done in the way that he knows how.
问题是
So, the question is,
你生拉尔夫的气
are you upset with Ralph
是因为你觉得他到处碍事
because you think he's screwing around
还是因为他不照你的计划走
or because he's not following your plan?
穿越者
Breacher!
也许我们能喝一杯
I thought maybe we could have a drink.
我不太清楚  但感觉你像是
I don't know, you strike me as kind of
爱喝龙舌兰的人  所以...
a tequila guy, so--
抗组胺剂  过敏药
糟糕
Oh, crap.
你回来受死了  穿越者
You've come back to die, Breacher.
到时候了  钉十字
The time has come, Crucifer.
去死吧吸血鬼  死吧
Die, vampire, die!
我的妈呀  他就要死了
Frack me, he's gonna die.
受死吧
Die!
等一等
Wait a second.
你退后
Hey, back up, yo.
长夜将歇天光亮  是时候让你晒晒太阳了
Yo, "Dust Till Dawn", I think it's time you saw some sun.
白痴  阳光伤不到这种吸血鬼
Idiot, sunlight doesn't hurt this type of vampire.
什么
What?
该跑路了
Time to go.
你说过你的反物质组织胺
You said your antimatter-histamine
会治好我
would cure me.
对  我是这么说过是吧
Yeah, I did say that, didn't I?
你骗了我
You lied to me.
你说过你能治好我的
You said you could fix me.
现在让我修理修理你
Now I'll fix you.
穿越者  停下吧
Breacher, stop!
你的震波攻击不管用了
Your vibe blasts don't work.
而且以后也不会管用了
And they're not gonna work.
为什么
Why not?
因为你的年龄
Because of your age.
我该早些告诉你的
I should have told you earlier.
只是  我知道我们的能力有多特别
It's just I know how special our powers are,
而你想到能恢复超能力时有多高兴
and you were so happy at the thought of having them back.
而且  我想你的女儿了
And I miss your daughter.
我只是想再见到她
I just wanted to see her again.
对不起  乔希
I'm sorry, Josh.
我恨你
I hate you.
你做得没错
You did the right thing.
是啊
Yeah.
谢谢
Thanks.
希望他能明白
Just wish he knew that.
克利福德在骗你
Clifford is lying to you.
他一直在给你用镇静眼泪
He is drugging you with sedative tears
好把你蒙在鼓里
to keep you idle.
求你了
Please.
求你了  记起来吧
Please, remember.
逃跑吧
Escape.
柠檬水新配方
New lemonade recipe.
文件名  柠檬水新配方
保存地址
相同文件名已存在
已存在
Already exists?
柠檬水新配方  H盘
求你千万别忘
Please don't forget.
他在骗你
He's lying to you.
他在给你下药
He's drugging you.
他是个魔鬼
He's a monster.
你必须逃跑
You must escape.
你总是用同一个名字保存这个文件
You always save it under the same name.
马上逃跑
Escape now.
每次你都能发现
Every time, you discover it.
你真的挺聪明的
It's quite clever, really.
一点都不辜负我对你的期望
I would expect nothing less from you.
这种事我经历过多少次了
How many times have I been through this?
太多次了
Too many.
但这不重要
But that is of no concern.
因为有了哭泣者的眼泪
Because with tears from the Weeper
再加上多米尼克·兰瑟的能力
mixed with Dominic Lanse's powers...
我能修改你的记忆
I can alter your memory.
所以你才创造了哭泣者
So that's why you created the Weeper.
你并不需要备用的宿主
You didn't need a potential host.
-他就是...  -为你而生的  没错
- He was-- - For you. Yes.
我知道正是令我爱上你的那个特质
I knew that the same thing in you that I fell in love with
有可能毁了我们
had the potential to destroy us.
就是你的人性
Your humanity.
我不能让你的人性挡了我们
I couldn't let that get in the way
实现目标的道路
of us achieving our goal.
大悟之道
The Enlightenment.
克利福德  我是你的妻子
Clifford, I am your wife--
而我爱你
And I love you.
但没了我  你什么都不是
But you are nothing without me.
这儿真是个出来玩的好地方
This is an interesting place to hang out.
你是来毁掉我坐冷板凳的乐趣的吗
You come here to suck the fun out of being benched?
我...
I...
不  我其实是来找你帮忙的
No, I came for your help actually.
你想要一个对什么都不能严肃对待的人帮你吗
You want help from the guy who can't take anything seriously?
听着  对不起
Look, I'm sorry.
我不应该那么快下论断的
I shouldn't have been so quick to judge.
但因为迪沃...
But with DeVoe...
超前了我们那么多步  这很...
so many steps ahead of us, it just--
看着你身处其中却玩世不恭的样子
To see you joking around in the middle of this
就让我觉得你没有好好把这当回事
just made me feel like you weren't taking it seriously.
我知道这事很严肃
I know this is serious.
我眼看着...
I watched...
我眼看着伊兹在我眼前死去
I watched Izzy die in front of me.
我吓得魂都丢了
I'm scared out of my mind.
你害怕的表现可是够怪的
Well, you know, you got an odd way of showing it.
不是所有人都是乔·韦斯特那样的
Yeah, well not everybody grew up with a super dad like Joe West
超级老爸带大的  可以轻松地表达感情
who makes it easy to talk about your feelings.
我十岁的时候  我爸爸抛下我和我妈出走了
When I was ten years old, my dad walked out on me and my mom.
我那时吓坏了
And I was terrified.
但我妈妈  她比我还害怕
But my mom, she was even more afraid.
所以我就开始讲笑话
So, you know, I just started making jokes.
开始插科打诨抖机灵
Started doing stupid gags and funny bits
偷放放屁坐
and whoopee cushions.
所有能驱赶她恐惧的事都做
Anything to push her fear away.
问题是一段时间后  我也开始
And the thing is, after a while I started to push
驱赶我的恐惧感了
my fear away too.
我完全不知道  拉尔夫
I had no idea, Ralph.
并不是说我不在乎打败迪沃这件事
It's not that I don't care about beating DeVoe.
也不是说我不在乎当个大英雄
It's not that I don't care about being a great hero.
只是从那以后  不论何时只要我一害怕
It's just that ever since then, anytime that I'm afraid,
我要么藏起来
I either hide...
要么讲笑话
Or I make jokes.
巴里  我们找到纳尔了  在中城博物馆
Barry, we found Null. Central City Museum.
你怎么想  想从冷板凳上下来吗
So what do you say? You want to get off the bench?
我真的需要你帮忙
I really could use your help.
要是非去不可的话
Well, if doo-ty calls.
-是吧  -好了
- Yes? - Yeah.
我们出发吧  好吗
Let's just go, all right?
中城博物馆募捐会
这才是我喜欢的派对
Now, this is my kind of party.
你们给我听着
Listen up, people!
所有金光闪闪珠光宝气的东西
Anything that shines, shimmers, or sparkles
都放到包里来
goes in the bag.
我喜欢来点蓝宝石
I love me some sapphires.
要是你以为我会把这拱手奉上
You're out of your mind
那你真是想疯了心了
if you think I'm giving this to you.
拱手奉上
Oh, give it to me?
不不不
No, no, no. No, no.
没必要这样
There's no need for that.
不用
No.
我自己动手拿就好
I'll just take it.
你们剩下这些人
And the rest of you,
交货啦
Sparklies
抓牢好吗  抓紧了
Just hold on, all right? Just hold on.
结束了  纳尔
It's over, Null.
你又回来了
So, back again.
还带了个朋友
Oh, with a friend.
其实是好朋友  我们周末出去玩
A good friend, actually. We hang out on the weekends.
我知道他住哪儿
I know where he lives--
-这次没车让你逃跑了  -是啊
- No getaway cars this time. - Right.
没有车
No cars.
但是有这么多乘客
But there are an awful lot of passengers.
天哪  她打算把所有人扔到大气里
Oh, my God, she's gonna send everyone into the atmosphere.
艾伦  你现在得把所有人转移走
Allen, you gotta get everyone out of there right now.
好的  所有人都转移了  她在哪
All right, that's everyone. Where is she?
不
No!
飞吧  闪电侠
Lookin' fly, Flash!
继续
Back to business.
天哪
Oh, God!
各位  我够不到他
Guys! I can't reach him!
西斯科  用缺口把他传送回来
Cisco, you have to breach him somewhere.
他的位置太高了
He's too high in the atmosphere.
我没法瞄准那么高的地方
I don't have aim like that.
让拉尔夫即兴发挥
Let Ralph improvise.
什么
What?
-什么  -是的
- What? - Yes.
用你的德比方式
Just do something Dibny-esque.
你自己决定  快点就好
Be your own hero. Just do it fast.
德比方式
Uh, Dibny-esque.
好的
Right.
都是为了这个亮闪闪的宝贝
All about that bling.
拉尔夫
Ralph!
这就是你的计划吗  他会掉下来摔死
That was your plan? He's gonna fall to his death.
我知道自己在做什么
I know what I'm doing.
快点  拉尔夫
Any time, Ralph!
3000米  他降落得很快
10,000 feet. He's falling fast.
1500米
Now 5,000 feet.
拉尔夫成功了
Ralph did it.
干得好  拉尔夫
Nice work, Ralph.
干得好
Nice work.
漂亮
Classy.
你这是在逗我吧
You've got to be kidding me.
拉尔夫
Ralph.
纳尔在管道监狱
All right, Null's in the pipeline.
她不是很高兴
She's not too happy about it.
在那里比她一个人呆着安全多了
Well, she's a lot safer there than she is on her own.
外面只剩一个公车超能力者了
Just one more bus meta out there.
最好在迪沃之前找到他
Better find him before DeVoe does.
哈里呢  他不是应该负责这件事吗
Where's Harry? Isn't he supposed to be working on it?
他嘟囔着些什么  然后走了
He grumbled something about something and then left.
我听到了哈里的话
I'm fluent in Harry grumble.
他说要去操作他的猫
He said he was gonna work his cat,
或者是去给自己做一个火鸡卷
or he was making himself a turkey wrap.
我要去一趟中城警局
Well, I'm gonna head over to CCPD,
调查一下这个艾德文·高斯
do some more digging on this Edwin Gauss.
拉尔夫
Ralph.
为什么一个声音听起来很恐怖的厄尔·考克斯
Why did a scared-sounding Earl Cox
打电话说他在帮你付账单
call me saying he was clearing your tab?
我
I...
我不知道  太奇怪了
I have no idea. That's really weird.
各位  可不可以来极速实验室帮个忙
Hey, guys, would you help me in the, uh, Speed Lab?
-好的  -谢谢
- Yeah. - Thanks.
-做即兴表演吗  -是的
- Work on some improv? - Yeah.
你今晚做得太好了  兄弟
You were great out there tonight, man.
谢谢
Thank you.
有好多人帮助我
I had a lot of help.
我还有一个很好的老师
And I had a great teacher.
你让我明白了
You helped me realize that
我不能总是把所有事情都看得太严肃
I can't always take everything so seriously.
哪怕是涉及到思考者的时候
Even when it comes to Thinker.
等等
Wait a second.
你是在跟我说  我  拉尔夫·德比
Are you telling me that I, Ralph Dibny,
给杰出的超级英雄巴里·艾伦上了一课吗
taught Barry Allen, superhero extraordinaire, a lesson?
-这意味着什么吗  -说明你是个大英雄
- What could this mean? - Means you're a great hero.
你的加入让这个团队变得更好
And you make this team better by being on it.
这个圈现在完整了
Ah, the circle is now complete.
我刚加入的时候只是一个初学者
When I came here I was but the learner.
现在我是个大师了
Now I am the master.
谦逊是种美德
It's also good to be humble.
我没法保持谦逊
But how can I be humble...
我现在骄傲到膨胀
When I am swollen with pride?
-西斯斯  -跳跃的水母啊
- Cisky! - Ah--jumpin' jellyfish!
我喜欢你的新装扮
I like your new threads.
是啊
Yeah.
我回到了我的地球
I went back to my earth.
从刀面上看到了我的倒影
Saw my reflection in my knife.
我看到一个老人
I saw an older man.
我很好奇
I'm curious.
你以前从来没照过镜子吗
Have you never looked in a mirror before?
我不是十几岁的女生
I'm not a teenage girl.
你不是十几岁的女生
Okay, you're not a teenage girl.
但是我发现
But I realized...
是时候挂起战衣退休了
time to hang up my coat.
这是我的新制服
This is my new uniform.
-喜欢吗  -喜欢
- Like it? - Yeah.
退休生活很适合你
Retirement suits you.
你接下来打算干什么
So, what do you do with all this time?
地球四十七有一个龙农场
There'e'a dragon farm on Earth-47
我一直想去看看
that I've always wanted to visit.
一个龙农场
A dragon farm?
带上你的卡丽熙
Get your Khaleesi on.
我不是卡丽熙
I'm not a Khaleesi.
你不是卡丽熙
Okay, you're not a Khaleesi.
我就是想告诉你  西斯斯
But I just wanted to tell you, Cisky,
永远再见了
good-bye forever.
等等  还有一件事
Oh, wait! Just one more thing.
既然我退休了
Now that I'm retired,
回收机构会有职位空缺
there's an opening at the Collection Agency.
我希望你能接替我的职务
I would like you to replace me.
等等  我不明白
Wait, I'm-- I'm confused.
你想经常见到我女儿
You want to see my daughter more.
去和她一起工作
Work with her.
你和辛西娅一起会成为无人能敌的二人组
Together you and Cynthia could be an unstoppable duo.
你觉得怎么样  震波
So what do you say, Vibe?
想成为新的穿越者吗
You want to be the new Breacher?
休息得怎么样  亲爱的
How was your rest, my love?
好极了
Wonderful.
我从来没感到如此精力充沛过
I've never felt more rejuvenated
准备好实现我们的梦想了
and ready to realize our dream.
克利福德
Clifford.
所有实验体超能力者身上的
The added combination of dark matter
新增暗物质组合
from all our subject metas is
正在摧毁这个宿主的身体
overwhelming this host's body.
我们还有多长时间
How long do we have?
按照现在这个速度
At the present rate,
只有一个星期
exactly one week's time.
不  我不会让这件事发生的
No, I will not allow it.
也许可以调整一下生物量指标
It may be possible to adjust the biomass index,
重新调试能量分配
recalibrate the energy distribution--
来延长现在这个宿主的生命
extend your current host's life.
奇怪
Odd.
关于这项调整的计划
There are already plans
已经被设计出一部分了
for such an adjustment partially designed.
我试着像你说的那样做了
I attempted the same course of action.
你做了个很好的开头
Well, you got quite a good start.
我可以在一个小时之内完成这个设计
I will be able to complete the designs in under an hour.
去休息吧  亲爱的
Rest, my love.
我会处理好一切
I will handle everything.
你总是会的
You always do.
等你完成了设计
And then when you complete your work,
我们就继续我们的旅程
we will continue on our journey
找到剩下的两个公车超能力者
to find the remaining two bus metas.
闪电侠小组抓到了11号目标
Team Flash has captured subject 11.
我们是时候开始行动了
Now it's time for us to act.
晚上好  威尔斯博士
Good evening, Dr. Wells.
距我们上一次交流已经过去了1078天
It's been 1,078 days since we last spoke.
我能怎样帮助您
How can I be of service?
你好  吉迪恩
Hello, Gideon.
这段时间发生了很多变化
A lot has changed since then.